comparestoreprices.co.uk 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy

Here is extended Information about Our privacy Policy 

## A. Personally Identifiable Information (PII).

CompareStorePrices.co.uk does not automatically collect any personal information about you. We do collect PII, including but not limited to your name, e-mail address, geographical location, age and gender, through membership registration, newsletter sign-up requests or promotional contests. Please note that it is not necessary for you to become a member in order to use many of the features on CompareStorePrices.co.uk.com, a non-member can easily see products and prices, perform searches, read reviews and take advantage of many other useful features on the site. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk also operates a free e-newsletter service - the CompareStorePrices.co.uk Update - to help you keep up-to-date with the best deals, contests and CompareStorePrices.co.uk news. This is an opt-in service so, as a member, you will receive the newsletter. To unsubscribe simply send an e-mail to [remove@CompareStorePrices.co.uk](mailto:remove@CompareStorePrices.co.uk) and include your e-mail address. 

The reason that we ask for this PII is to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on the Site, and to contact you when necessary in connection with any promotions you participate in. 

We also use this information for internal business purposes, such as aggregating the data to help us to create a profile of CompareStorePrices.co.uk visitors, as a whole, so that we can; a) build a better understanding of our users and enhance the services we offer, and b) attract advertisers to spend money on CompareStorePrices.co.uk, thus enabling our free price comparison service to operate. 

Unless you direct us not to, we may use your personal information to contact you about offers or promotions from CompareStorePrices.co.uk and selected third parties we think you would be interested in. 

## B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

CompareStorePrices.co.uk uses cookies (a small text file containing a unique string of numbers or letters that is placed on a computer) to ‘remember’ your computer when you visit the site. Using cookies helps us serve ads, take polls and better manage the services we offer. This will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. Cookies do not recognize you as a person, just your computer. They cannot be used to obtain other information from your hard drive. 

For each visitor to our website, our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Upon visiting our website, we assign each visitor a unique ID that is used to track visitor traffic patterns within our website. We also collect aggregate and user-specific information on the pages that visitors access or visit. We reserve the right to retain all website traffic reporting data as long as may be reasonably necessary for accounting and auditing purposes. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk may use third party vendors to help us operate our business and this Site or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by CompareStorePrices.co.uk. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk and/or our marketing partners may enhance and/or merge PII with commercially-available third party data collected from other sources in an effort to ensure that the messages being sent to the consumer in online and/or offline marketing programs are relevant to their interests. In the event we enhance and/or merge such personally identifiable information with data collected from other sources, we will take reasonable steps to maintain the integrity and quality of that information. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk may share PII (including information that has been enhanced with information from other sources) with co-branded partners, advertisers, third party marketers, our affiliated entities for their online and/or offline marketing programs or in connection with the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial asset, reorganization or liquidation of any CompareStorePrices.co.uk division. 

Please note that while CompareStorePrices.co.uk encourages merchants and marketing partners to adopt responsible approaches to online marketing, we are not responsible for the information practices of our merchants or marketing partners. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by such third parties is subject to their respective privacy policies, which may differ from this policy. Please be sure to review their policy prior to providing any information. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk may release account and any other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of CompareStorePrices.co.uk or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

### III. Consumer Choice And Access

If at anytime you no longer wish to receive offers from a CompareStorePrices.co.uk, you may "unsubscribe" by sending an email to [remove@CompareStorePrices.co.uk](mailto:remove@CompareStorePrices.co.uk) or by using the unsubscribe option on this page. In compliance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, you will be removed entirely from our email list and will no longer receive offers from us. If you have registered or submitted PII under more than one email account, you must submit separate unsubscribe requests from each account. 

The Cookies we use do not have an "opt-out" option, yet you still have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in your Internet browser. Please see your browser supplier's website for details on how to do this. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk sends a confirming email for each member registration. You may change, correct or update your information by email by contacting [privacy@CompareStorePrices.co.uk](mailto:privacy@CompareStorePrices.co.uk) Changing or deleting your information or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from the CompareStorePrices.co.uk will change or delete the data only in our database for purposes of transacting future business on our sites and for managing future communications from CompareStorePrices.co.uk. These changes and deletions will not change or delete information already collected as part of a particular transaction. 

### IV. Security

CompareStorePrices.co.uk employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Any data that is stored on CompareStorePrices.co.uk’s servers are treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Access is password-protected and limited to individuals at whose job responsibilities require the access. 

No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of CompareStorePrices.co.uk to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your PII, CompareStorePrices.co.uk cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with us. 

### V. Consent And Changes

CompareStorePrices.co.uk may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by CompareStorePrices.co.uk prior to the effective date of the policy change unless we provide you direct notice and the opportunity to opt-out of such proposed change. 

### VI. Children's Privacy And Spam

CompareStorePrices.co.uk is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. CompareStorePrices.co.uk's web sites, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. If you believe your child has provided CompareStorePrices.co.uk with any personally identifiable data by registering at a CompareStorePrices.co.uk web site, please contact [privacy@CompareStorePrices.co.uk](mailto:privacy@CompareStorePrices.co.uk) to have them removed. 

CompareStorePrices.co.uk is committed to proper Internet practices and full compliance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. It is our policy to prohibit the sending of unsolicited or "Spam" email by CompareStorePrices.co.uk or any of its marketing partners. 

### VII. Data Processing

You acknowledge that CompareStorePrices.co.uk operates in the United State and the European Union and agree to (i) permit CompareStorePrices.co.uk to transmit and use your User information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to affect the services and transactions provided by this Site; and (ii) that such use by CompareStorePrices.co.uk shall be subject to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Statement and our Terms and Conditions. 

### VIII. Limitation Of Liability, Third Party Information & Language

You understand and agree that any dispute over privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy and our terms and conditions (including limitations on damages, and arbitration of disputes). You agree that CompareStorePrices.co.uk’s liability for any breach of this privacy policy shall be limited to the value of the transactions or services provided to you by CompareStorePrices.co.uk to the extent such claim is not otherwise barred by our terms and conditions. Nothing in this agreement limits or excludes either party's liability for fraud or for negligence causing death or personal injury. 

You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to CompareStorePrices.co.uk with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's data has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal data; (c) which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. 

## Contact Us

### Additional Information.

If you have a question that was not addressed in this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by: 

1\. Sending an e-mail request to [privacy@CompareStorePrices.co.uk](mailto:privacy@CompareStorePrices.co.uk) ; or 

2\. Sending a letter via Mail to: Advanced System Technologies Ltd, Sentinel House, 10-12 Massetts Road, Horley, Surrey, RH6 7DE
